<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Osea Spaces</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Osea Spaces</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Colorful loft partition in Amsterdam Apartment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/amsterdam-loft-partition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/amsterdam-loft-partition/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this loft style-apartment, living room and bedroom were initially separated by a solid wall. To create a greater sense of spaciousness and bring more natural light into the bedroom, we introduced a glass and metal partition with a curved corner and slim doors that open from floor to ceiling. The design draws inspiration from Parisian café facades, featuring slim metal frames, and large glass panels. The steel is finished in a typical French soft green hue.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunny orangery in garden, Normandy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/normandy-orangery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/normandy-orangery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This orangery was designed and decorated for a rural family home in Normandy. To make it possible to enjoy the garden and sunlight year-round, we designed and built an orangery that allows natural light to flood the space, and that seamlessly blends with the outdoor environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The orangery features a modern slim steel frame and a lean-to glass roof. The wide doors, which open outward, offer an open connection between the interior and the garden, allowing for natural ventilation during the summer months.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic room partition with sliding doors in Amsterdam Apartment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/amsterdam-sliding-doors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/amsterdam-sliding-doors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this apartment, several rooms had to be reconfigured to maximize space. To create distinct areas while maintaining the flow of natural light, we installed subtle steel room partitions with large sliding doors featuring fluted glass.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The fluted glass strikes a balance, offering privacy in each room while allowing light to filter through, creating a dynamic, colorful effect. The sliding doors can be fully opened, enabling flexible use of space as needed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
